mvelopes.com 2004-12-08

# Personal budgeting software to plan a home budget and do money management

Mvelopes Privacy Policy

At In2M Corporation, we dedicate ourselves to revolutionizing the way people live and businesses work. As a subscriber to In2M, you don't have to worry about the security and confidentiality of your personal information. Just like you, we want all of your personal information kept that way—personal and private. To demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices, we have adopted leading industry privacy guidelines. This notice describes our privacy statement and practices followed by In2M.

Federal legislation requires us to provide In2M users who register for Mvelopes® services with a description of our information collection and sharing practices. 

This document, effective July 1, 2001, specifically describes how we handle your personally identifiable information and applies to financial products and services for your personal use provided by In2M.

**Information Collection and Use**  
In2M is the owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information except as disclosed in this statement. Whenever we ask for additional or optional information, we identify those fields appropriately so that you know what information is required to provide the requested service. To maximize the value of our services, we may request or collect information from you when you visit our Web sites. This privacy statement tells you what is being collected, how it is collected, by whom it is being collected, why it is being collected and to whom it may be disclosed. 

Mvelopes® service registration. In order to provide you with the best support possible, we request Mvelopes Personal users to register with In2M. When you register, you'll be asked to provide your name, address, phone number and e-mail address. We will also ask you for personal survey information about why you subscribed Mvelopes Personal. The information gathered from it will help us provide you with better products and services in the future. Occasionally, we may also use your e-mail address to offer you the opportunity to provide input to us via other surveys that will help us improve our products and services.

In2M’s Mvelopes Service. When you enroll for service, you will be asked to select a username and password, and to provide us with your full name, address, zip code, phone number and e-mail address. We use your username and password to verify your identity, which is required to give you access to your Mvelope’s service. For access to financial, investment, and credit card statement download services, we ask you to provide additional information such as an account number and a personal identification number (PIN). We will also need to identify you if you forget your password, by asking for your mother's maiden name or other unique identifier. We use this information to verify your accounts with your financial institutions and to provide you with access to the services you are requesting. We also ask for your credit card number to process your initial and all your subsequent payments. The contact information is required to establish your service with the financial institutions, brokerage houses and credit card companies of your choice. Your e-mail address will be used as our primary source of contact with you regarding your service. In the event that you receive In2M newsletters that you no longer wish to receive, you may unsubscribe at the subscription center or by following the instructions provided in each e-mail newsletter. We do not share your personal information with third parties except as required to fulfill your request for service and as required by law. 

In2M bill payment. In2M bill payment is a Web-based service that allows you to view and pay your bills on the Internet.The service is currently provided by a third party. Before using this service, please carefully review the associated privacy statement for this service.

Technical and product support. In order to provide you with technical and product support, we ask for your name and e-mail address. We may use your contact information in order to contact you regarding service updates or specific support questions. We may also contact you for additional opportunities to provide feedback on our products and services unless you request not to receive such communications. 

Contests and surveys. From time to time, we may offer you the option to participate in contests or surveys. If you would like to participate, we may ask you for contact information, preferences or other information. This information may be used to conduct research, improve our offerings or award prizes. Our contests may have separate rules and we will identify how the information that you supply will be used in each case. 

Information about your computer or browser. In2M collects such information so that we may analyze trends, administer the site and gather broad demographic information in order to provide our users with the best possible Web experience, appropriate products or services and to format e-mail messages that best align with your computer's capabilities. This information is collected in a generic aggregate format and is not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Links to other sites. In2M Web sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that In2M is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. Our co-branded sites are clearly identified by both an In2M and a partner's logo. On these sites In2M and its partners may collect personal information. Please also review the privacy statements of our partners to determine how they will use the information they collect. In2M is not responsible for the actions of any third parties. 

Web site cookie usage. In order to better serve you and protect your account information, we use "cookies," nuggets of data that are stored on your hard drive as a file. We use cookies to verify who you are while using our Web sites. Cookies make it easier, quicker, and more secure for you to log into and use our Web sites. 

Cookies do not compromise privacy or personally identify users. Their data is usually stored on your computer's hard drive as a file or folder called "cookies," and you can delete this file anytime you choose. The cookies used on our Web sites are only valid for the current session and shortly become invalid. Cookies created by one site will only work with that specific site. Site A, for example, cannot read cookies generated by Site B and then use that information for purposes for which it was not intended. 

Referrals. If users elect to use our referral service for informing others about our site or products, we ask them for a name, phone and e-mail address for themselves and for the person/people being referred. In2M will automatically send the referred party/parties a one-time e-mail or call them one time inviting them to visit the site or make a purchase. In2M stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail or making this one-time phone call. The referred party may contact In2M at privacy@in2m.com to request the removal of this information from the referral database. 

Former customers. We treat information concerning our former customers the same way we treat information about our current customers. 

Children. Because of the financial nature of our business, our Web sites are not designed to appeal to children under the age of 18. Therefore, we don't knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from children. 

**Access to Your Information**  
In2M does not share your personally identifiable information with third parties except as explained in this privacy statement. The information you provide us will only be shared under limited circumstances. These include: With service providers. In some cases, we will employ or work with service providers such as marketing or security consultants, temporary workers, third-party software developers or outsourcers to complete a business process or provide a service on our behalf. For example, we may use service providers to deliver products, to offer online software applications or to send e-mails on our behalf. While this may require that we share some information, we will only share information that the service provider must have to perform the requested services. For example, a service provider who delivers products on our behalf would need to have a delivery address. However, these service providers are strictly prohibited from using your information for any purpose other than to act on our behalf.   
For legal reasons. In some cases we may be required to disclose certain information to comply with the law, an investigation or a legal process, such as a court order or subpoena. 

In case of a sale of a business. Your information may be transferred in connection with a sale, merger, transfer, exchange or other disposition (whether of assets, stock or otherwise) of all or a portion of a business of In2M or its subsidiaries. 

**Choice/Opt Out**  
We give you the opportunity to keep us from using or sharing the personally identifiable information that you provide to us for purposes other than those explained in this statement. We will provide you the opportunity to opt-out of secondary uses of personally identifiable information you provide us, whenever we gather it. Simply notify us during the information collection process or contact us at privacy @ in2m.com.

We may send site and service announcement updates. You are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about service. We communicate with you to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to your account by phone or e-mail.

**Security Safeguards**

Mvelopes employs industry-standard physical, electronic and procedural security safeguards to help protect the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. Whenever we prompt you to transmit sensitive information, such as a credit card number, we support encryption of your data as it is transmitted.   
In2M uses the latest technology to protect your account information from exposure to unauthorized persons. Below are some of the components of this security system:

  * A username and password are required to access the Mvelopes online service. 
  * After entering a username or password incorrectly three times, access to an account is blocked. 
  * Up to 256-bit encryption scrambles your sensitive transmissions made via the Internet. 

You are responsible for protecting the secrecy of your Password in accordance with the terms contained in the Mvelopes Online Service Agreement. We recommend you not store secure pages in your cache or leave your computer unattended while you are logged in to Mvelopes online service or while shopping the In2M Web site.

Although no security measures are foolproof, we work diligently to protect personally identifiable information stored on the sites' servers from unauthorized access using industry-standard available computer security products, such as firewalls, as well as carefully developed security procedures and practices. 

**Correcting/Updating Personal Information**  
At our Web site, we provide you the opportunity to update or correct your account, financial and credit card download information. You may review and update your contact information by phoning In2M Customer Support at 1 866 Mvelopes (683-5673).

**Changes to Our Privacy Statement**  
Before we make significant changes to our privacy statement or practices with respect to how we use personally identifiable information, we'll post those changes to this privacy statement at least 30 days before they take effect.

**How to Contact In2M**  
Questions regarding the In2M Web sites' privacy statement, our information practices or other aspects of privacy on our Web sites should be directed to privacyin2m.com.
